Life Do-Over Device
My. What a smart young boy, little Toshio is!
I know how to write!
Oh, really?
Only his name, though!
You really are smart!
I'm so moved!
You only just turned four, right?
I know how to write in Kanji.
'Tree cuukeech 'minuch 'ne equals two cuukeech.
Wow, you know maths too!
But that's too easy!
Know what 13 plus 26 is?
I do. It's 39.
Nobita, go play by yourself for a while.
It's not fair!
I know way more than he does,
but mum never praises ME!
Well, sure. You're in 4th grade now.
4 years old, 4th grade, who cares? It's all 4!
I wish I could be 4-year old again,
knowing what I know now.
Sure. That's easy enough!
It is?!
The "Life Do-Over Device"!
Everyone has moments in their life that they wish they could do over.
This device lets you go back.
You can relive those moments differently.
While keeping my current
intellect and physical strength?
Of course! That way you won't make the same mistake.
What age do you want to go back to?
4!
Got'cha!
There!
I don't need glasses.
I'm 4 again!
What is this place?
What was I doin' here, I wonder?
Oh yeah, this was the lumberyard.
I remember now.
I 'ched to play here all the time. It hasn't changed a bit!
What're ya doin' up dere, Nobita-kun?
Hide and seek ain't fun...
If you 'dun look for us!
Giant, Suneo and Shizuka-chan!
You're all so adorable!
Don't call me adorable!
I see. Giant was as violent as ever always.
Stop picking on the weak!
Being helped by a girl!
Nobita's such a crybaby!
They've been making fun of me even in the past.
Letz' play sumthin' more incheresting!
How 'bout school?
I'll be the teacher!
No, I'll be the teacher.
No, me.
I know how to write!
So do I.
Me too!
'Awright, let's all write our names!
See?
Me too.
Now me!
How dirty your handwriting is!
Then, can you write in Kanji?
Of course, I can!
Nobi-chan, you can write in Kanji?
Yes, of course!
He's lying. This is just scribbles.
But I wrote using real Kanji!
I'll ask a grown-up.
'Xcuse me, michter!
What is it, young girl?
Unbelievable! You really wrote these Kanji?
So it is the real Kanji?!
What a refined handwriting!
I won't accept this!
That's cheating!
Take that!
What? My Nobi-chan made them cry?
But I just pushed them!
Actually I'm from the Genius' Education Society.
Genius' Education Society?
What? My Nobi-chan wrote this?!
I know how to write all kinds of words.
Okay, here's the next problem.
I have 3 apples and 3 bananas. How many is that?
6.
Well, I'm surprised, this is quite an amazing feat for just a 4-year old boy.
I recommend sending him to an elementary school.
He's as mature as an 2nd grader.
Hey, I'm actually 4th grader!
Wow, really?
He passed every test with authority. He's a genius!
We are blessed.
He'll be able to enter the Tokyo University like this.
Not just that, he'll be a great scholar.
How wonderful!
FoGonna take a leak?
Yup.
A monster!
Shh! It's me!
Looks like you had lot of fun.
Now let's go home!
Forget it! Everyone's delighted having me here!
I'm a genius here. They say I'm gonna eventually grow up to become the Prime Minister of Japan!
I wanna become a grown-up like this!
No can do. You can't rely on my gadgets.
You need to grow up with your own efforts!
Says who?
Then see your future for yourself with the "Time TV".
This will show you what happens if you stay here.
FIrst, a year from now on!
Everyone's getting their test papers back.
I got 100 points. Isn't that amazing?
Now let's see you as a fourth grader.
Nobita!
I know you got another 0!
You need to study harder!
I'm just about to.
What's going on here?!
Remember, you're still at a second grade level.
But since you never study in this world...
...you have no idea how to actually do it.
Now let's see you as an adult...
Don't wanna! Had enough!
I'll go back!
Good boy!
I would like to go back.
Now you understand that the path
to success is through hard work!
Alright! I'm gonna study!
Great!
I'm gonna study hard and invent a device!
But what device?
I'll invent a device that makes
you smart without studying!
How hopeless! He still doesn't understand!